Sara Meadows

sameads9@gmail.com | 314.691.3980 | St. Louis, MO

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/sara-meadows

GitHub

aithub.com/sarameadows

Portfolio

https://sarameadows.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with an artistic background, well-known as a creative problem solver, passionate about developing applications with a beautiful interface and an engaging user experience. I enjoy collaborating with others as well as learning about the latest technologies as part of my curious and analytical nature.

Technical Skills

Frontend: HTML5, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, AJAX

Backend: MySQL, MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node, Handlebars, Webpack, APIs

Education

Washington University, St. Louis

October 2022

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Maryville University, St. Louis

December 2021

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Photography, Minor in Studio Art

Relevant Work Experience

Esther & Mila

June 2022 - Present

Creative Production Lead

St. Louis, MO

 Wordpress website management, Product and Lifestyle Photography, Jewelry Designer, Brand development, Inventory management, Sales

Saettele Jewelers October 2021 - June 2022

Sales Associate & Marketing Assistant

St. Louis. MO

Wordpress website management, Product Photography, Sales, Client relations, Social Media

Whitebridge Pet Brands

August 2018 - September 2019

Marketing Assistant

St. Louis, MO

 Optimized influencer program for several pet brands, Inventory management, Assisted with projects for Chewy and Amazon

Additional Work Experience

Craft Alliance June 2021 - April 2022

Metal and Glass Faculty
St. Louis, MO

Adidas April 2019 - October 2020

Supervisor St. Louis, MO

Awards/Honors

ALD Honor Society, 2018-2021 / Dean's List, 2017-2021 / Maryville's Innovators of Tomorrow, 2017